A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992., Extent: 45.15 cubic feet (129 boxes). (Box 1-129)
  - Public Library files, 1971-1986.
    - Botetourt County Library, 1979-1981. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1977-1979. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1971-1976. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1983-1985. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1979-1982. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1978-1981. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Buckingham County Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Appomattox Regional Library), 1980-1985. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Appomattox Regional Library), 1971-1979. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Carroll Public Library, 1971-1982. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Caroline Library, Inc., 1980-1985. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1980-1981. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1976-1979. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1972-1976. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1971. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library, 1982-1985. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library, 1971-1981. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1982-1985. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1979-1981. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1971-1978. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Charles City County - The Heritage Library.
    - Charlotte County Free Library, 1971-1984. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Charlottesville - See Jefferson-Madison Regional Library.
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Cheasapeake Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1979-1985. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1976-1978. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Clifton Forge Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Clifton Forge Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Colonial Heights Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Community Library, The, 1971-1972. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Covington - See Charles P. Jones Memorial Library.
    - Culpeper Town and County Library, 1980-1985. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Culpeper Town and County Library, 1971-1979. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Cumberland County Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Danville Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Danville Public Library, 191971-1979. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Dickenson County - See Lonesome Pine Regional Library.
    - Dinwiddie County - See Appomattox Regional Library.
    - Eastern Shore Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library, 1978-1981. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library, 1971-1977. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Edinburg Community Library, 1971-1984. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Essex Public Library, 1972-1985. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1980-1981. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1978-1979. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1978. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1976. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1974-1975. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1972-1973. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Falls Church - See Mary Riley Styles Public Library.
    - Fauquier County Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fauquier County Public Library, 1977-1980. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Fauquier County Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Fluvanna County Library, 1982-1985. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County Library, 1971-1981. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Fredericksburg - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library.
    - Franklin County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Franklin County Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Franklin County Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Front Royal - See Samuels Public Library.
    - Galax-Carroll Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Galax-Carroll Regional Library, 1978-1981. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Galax-Carroll Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Giles County - See Narrows Public Library.
    - Gloucester Library, 1975-1985. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Greene County - See Jefferson-Madison Regional Library.
    - Halifax County-South Boston Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Halifax County-South Boston Regional Library, 1978-1981. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Halifax County-South Boston Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Hampton - See Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library.
    - Handley Library, The, 1981-1985. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Handley Library, The, 1978-1980. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Handley Library, The, 1971-1977. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Hanover County - See Pamunkey Regional Library.
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1976-1980. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Henry County - See Blue Ridge Regional Library.
    - Heritage Library, The, 1985. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Highland County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Hopewell - See Appomattox Regional Library and Maude Langhorne Nelson Library.
    - Isle of Wight County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library.
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1985-1986. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1983-1984. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1981-1982. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1979-1980. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1977-1978. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1975-1976. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1971-1974. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Jones Memorial Library, 1971-1982. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - King and Queen County Public Library, 1985. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - King George County - See Lewis Edgerton Smoot Memorail Library.
    - King William County - See Pamunkey Regional Library.
    - Lancaster County Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Lewis Edgerton Smoot Memorial Library, 1972-1985. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1984-1985. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1981-1983. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1978-1980. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1975-1977. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1974-1975. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1973-1974. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1971-1972. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1974-1981. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Louisa County - See Jefferson-Madison Regional Library.
    - Lunenburg County - See Southside Regional Library.
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1971-1980. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - McIntire Public Library - See also Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1971-1972. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Madison County Library, Inc., 1980-1985. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Madison County Library, 1971-1979. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Mathews Memorial Library, 1980-1985. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Mathews Memorial Library, 1971-1979. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Martinsville Memorial Public Library - See also Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Maude Langhorne Nelson Library, 1971-1974. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Mary Riley Styles Public Library (Falls Church), 191982-1985. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Mary Riley Styles Public Library (Falls Church), 1979-1981. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Mary Riley Styles Public Library (Falls Church), 19. (Box 66)
    - Mecklenburg County - See Southside Regional Library
    - Montgomery-Floyd Regional Library, 1981-1985. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery-Floyd Regional Library, 1978-1981. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery-Floyd Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Montgomery-Floyd Regional Library, 1971-1985. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Nansemond County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library.
    - Narrows Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Narrows Public Library, 1971-1980. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Nelson County - See Jefferson-Madison Regional Library.
    - New Market Area Library, 1977-1984. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1975-1980. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1971-1974. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1976-1979. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Northumberland Memorial Library, 1971-1985. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Nottoway County Library, 1980-1985. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Nottoway County Library, 1971-1979. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1980-1985. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1971-1979. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Patrick County - See Blue Ridge Regional Library.
    - Patrick Henry Memorial Library, 1978-1984. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1977-1979. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1971-1980. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1977-1979. (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1971-1977. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Poquoson Public Library, 1975-1985. (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1979-1985. (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Powhatan County Public Library, 1971-1985. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Prince Edward Public Library, 1984. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Prince George County - See Appomattox Regional Library.
    - Prince William Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1976-1978. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1982-1985. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1979-1981. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1971-1978. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Purcellville Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1971-1974. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Radford Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Radford Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1981-1985. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1977-1980. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1971-1976. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1971-1980. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1977-1981. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Roanoke Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke Public Library, 1975-1979. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Roanoke Public Library, 1971-1974. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1984-1985. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1982-1983. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1980-1981. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1979. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Rockingham Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Rockingham Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Rockingham Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Salem Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Salem Public Library, 1974-1980. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Samuels Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Samuels Public Library, 1978-1981. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Samuels Public Library, 1971-1977. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah County Library, 1971-1985. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Smithfield - See Benjamin P. Chapman Memorial Library.
    - Smyth-Bland Regional Library, 1981-1985. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Smyth-Bland Regional Library, 1978-1980. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Smyth-Bland Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Southampton County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library.
    - Southside Regional Library, 1981-1985. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Southside Regional Library, 1971-1980. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Spotsylvania County - See also Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1984. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Stafford County - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library.
    - Staunton Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Strasburg Community Library, 1971-1984. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Suffolk - See Morgan Memorial Library.
    - Surry County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library.
    - Sussex County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library.
    - Tazewell County Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Tazewell County Public Library, 1977-1980. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Tazewell County Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Thomas Balch Library - See also Loudoun County Public Library, 1971-1973. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Timbrook Library (Lynchburg), 1972. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Urbanna Public Library, 1980-1985. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Urbanna Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1984-1985. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1980-1983. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1977-1979. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1974-1976. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1971-1973. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1983-1985. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1980-1982. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1978-1979. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1971-1977. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1983-1985. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1982. (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1979-1981. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1976-1980. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Westmoreland County - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library.
    - Williamsburg Regional Library, 1981-1985. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Williamsburg Regional Library, 1978-1980. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Williamsburg Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Winchester - See The Handley Library.
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1982-1985. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1979-1981. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1975-1978. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1974. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1971-1973. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - York County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Director's general correspondence, 1941-1965.
    This sub-series consists of 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically and thereunder chronologically. This series includes A-L and N. The remainder of this subseries is missing and has not been located.
    - General correspondence - A, 1958-1965. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence - A, 1947-1957. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - B, 1960-1966. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - B, 1954-1959. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - B, 1948-1953. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - C, 1964-1965. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - C, 1960-1963. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - C, 1958-1959. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - C, 1955-1957. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - C, 1953-1954. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence - C, 1948-1952. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - D, 1957-1965. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - D, 1948-1956. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - E, 1941-1965. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - F, 1965. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - F, 1957-1964. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - F, 1941-1956. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - G, 1957-1965. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - G, 1952-1956. (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence - G, 1941-1951. (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence - H, 1960-1965. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence - H, 1952-1959. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - H, 1941-1951. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - I, 1958-1965. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - I, 1941-1957. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - J, 1950-1965. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - J, 1945-1949. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - K, 1958-1960. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - L, 1960-1965. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - L, 1951-1959. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence - L, 1951-1950. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence - N, 1958-1959. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Director's general correspondence, 1966-1977.
    This sub-series consists of 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically and thereunder chronologically.
    - General correspondence - A, 1974-1977. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - A, 1972-1973. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - A, 1966-1972. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - B, 1972-1977. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - B, 1966-1971. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - C, 1972-1977. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - C, 1969-1971. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - C, 1966-1968. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - D, 1972-1977. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence - D, 1966-1971. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence - E, 1966-1977. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence - F, 1970-1976. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - F, 1966-1969. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - F, 1966-1969. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - G, 1972-1977. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - G, 1966-1971. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - I, 1966-1976. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - J, 1966-1975. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - K, 1969-1977. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - K, 1960-1968. (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence - L, 1966-1977. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence - M, 1972-1977. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence - M, 1969-1971. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence - M, 1966-1968. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence - N, 1969-1977. (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence - N, 1966-1968. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence - O, 1966-1976. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence - P, 1966-1977. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence - Q, 1966-1972. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence - R, 1966-1977. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence - S, 1972-1977. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence - S, 1966-1971. (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence - T, 1966-1977. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence - U-V, 1965-1977. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence - W, 1970-1977. (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence - W, 1966-1969. (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence - X-Z, 1968-1976. (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Public Library Consultant Reports, 1979-1987.
    This sub-series consists of 2 boxes and is arranged alphabetically, and chronologically thereunder.
    - Annual reports, 1979-1980. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Annual reports, 1980-1981. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Annual reports, 1981-1982. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Annual reports, 1984-1985. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Annual report - Public Library Development Division, 1986-1987. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979 Jan--Mar. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Quarterly reports, 1979 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly reports, 1980 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Quarterly reports, 1980 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly reports, 1980 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly reports, 1980 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly reports, 1981 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Quarterly reports, 1981 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly reports, 1981 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Quarterly reports, 1981 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Quarterly reports, 1982 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Quarterly reports, 1982 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Quarterly reports, 1982 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Quarterly reports, 1982 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Quarterly reports, 1983 Jan-Mar. (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Quarterly reports, 1983 Apr-June. (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Quarterly reports, 1983 July-Sept. (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Quarterly reports, 1983 Oct-Dec. (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Quarterly reports, 1984 Jan-Mar. (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Quarterly reports, 1984 Apr-June. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly reports, 1984 July-Sept. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly reports, 1984 Oct-Dec. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly reports, 1985 July-Sept. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Quarterly reports, 1985 Oct-Dec. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly reports, 1986 Jan-Mar. (Box 88, Folder 7)